[{"answer": "Just fine, thank you.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "Couldn't be better.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "Life good?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well, at my age, you do that.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "Do you ever stop to actually look back and think, good god?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "I love what happened because I had -- all my uncles and aunts and nieces and nephews, they were all good people, hard working people.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "What do you think when you think back to those days?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "They just like -- well, besides great food.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "What values did they instill in you, that community you had, family and friends?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "That's what happened, actually.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "And you sing for your supper, would you?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "I remember very clearly saying, this is who I am.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Is that when you got that excitement, that you thought this is for me?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "ENNETT: It's never a bother for me.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "You know you get to go and sing or paint or whatever it may be, but everything you do, you love doing, don't you?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I started with the \"Duets I.\" It was so successful that Sony Columbia said please do another one like that.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "Do any of the ones on this album match up in quality of voice to the greats like Sinatra or it is different these days?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "They were all very professional, they were all prepared.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Is it as good?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "She was so sweet to everybody, to every stage hand and everybody, thank you for being so nice to me and all that.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Especially in your great country Britain.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "I tell you, it was about six months.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "How long was that period for you when you were slightly feeling maybe it's over?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "I don't feel like ever retiring.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Having had all this success, how did that period make you feel?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "I learned -- Jack Rolands, Woody Allen's manager, he said that he managed Lenny Bruce years ago, who's a brilliant man.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "When you see the younger stars these days or younger entertainer, they're not called necessarily stars, but when you see how much more available drugs now are even than they were in your day perhaps, does it concern you?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "It was a blessing.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Do you feel fortunate that you were able to do that?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Well, that's right.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "Did you have friends, colleagues and so on who were not so fortunate, who just ended up being ruined by drugs?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Mm-hmm, yes.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Because to me she was one of the best singer/songwriters to have emerged in a very, very long time, wasn't she?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Really.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "I was at home.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Where were you, Tony, when you heard that she died?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "My son called me up and told me she just died.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "How did you hear about it?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Could you tell?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "It is very sad.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Very sad, isn't it?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "At any given moment you can learn.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "I mean, when people are huge entertainers, it brings with it particular pressures, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "No, I -- actually --", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Squeaky clean as imagine you must be?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "I have a glass of wine at night.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "You drink -- do you drink at all?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Completely.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Presumably the cocaine days are behind you now, Tony?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "It's something you can't teach.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "How important is self-discipline for a singer?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "What's happening to me right now is I have a new album, I'm not just plugging this.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "And it's dangerous, isn't it?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "It meant everything.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "How much -- how much of your ability to be successful for so long do you think is down to having strong people like your mother in your early life?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "That's my signature song.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Well, that was your theme tune, isn't it, really, \"I Left My Heart in San Francisco\"?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Do you ever get tired of singing it?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "ENNETT: I'd sing the last line of that song.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "If you had five minutes to live, what song would you sing?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "\"Your golden sun will shine for me.\"", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Would you?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "I think it's the greatest accomplishment that the United States ever came up with.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Did you think then when Martin Luther King was assassinated, did you think in your lifetime, you would see a black president in America?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "It's a dream of mine that someday the world will pick themselves up by their boot straps and better themselves, walk toward humanity, realize what a gift it is to be alive and to be on this planet.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "What was driving you at the time?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Was that -- was that how you felt?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "But do you feel that war is ever justified?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "It's a very difficult question, because I think we should have a society of highly educated, intelligent people that will think realistically about how to do things.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "With all the collateral damage that comes?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Was that really the point you were making?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Well, America -- to be an American is you're ahead of everybody on the planet.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "What does it mean to you to be an American?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "-- around the world, it would a very different world, right?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "You know, I started working with Tony -- my dad --", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "How did you go about this?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "And at a time when rock 'n' roll people stopped taking chances, Tony never stopped.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Was that part of your thinking?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Well, yes, but I don't have to be.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "I mean, do you feel very protective towards your father?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Well, yes, but I'm socked about what you're saying because it's humorous for me.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Do you look at young people today and say, I wish you were just more respectful and polite?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "You could not get in the room.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Yes, I think it's a shame.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "So you just wonder, where are we going?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Yes, he is.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Isn't he awesome?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Did you enjoy that?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "When it comes to entertainment or just --", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "If I was to pin you down and say, right, what has been the greatest moment of your life, what would you say it's been?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Yes, \"Fly Me to the Moon.\"", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "-- you retire?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "I mean, I think, you know, again, it's -- I'm doing a documentary called \"The Zen of Tony Bennett,\" and it is that focus.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Danny, what do you think's been the secret of your father's success, if you were to try and crystallize it, what would you say?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "You work out every day?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "I believe that's absolutely correct, the way -- what you described is the way I feel.", "docId": "111010pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Is it -- is it just because you do something you love, just working as hard as you can to keep the passion burning?", "qSentId": 555}]